

MC-112, College Ring 6, Bremen, 28759, Germany

🛘 (+49) 1511-5661770 | 🗷 theparthshukla@gmail.com | 🎢 www.parthshukla.dev | 🖸 theparthshukla | 🛅 theparthshukla

"Do, or do not. There is no try."

Summary _

Creative and engaged third year Computer Science student and Software Developer with experience in design and backend development. Interested in using my passion for problem solving to build better solutions for challenging tasks and learning new technologies and tools.

Education

Jacobs University Bremen, Germany

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Aug. 2019 - Present

• Specialization in Databases and Web Applications, Human-Computer Interaction, Digital Design and Computer Vision.

Work Experience _____

Solactive AG Berlin, Germany

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Sep. 2020 - Present

- · Designed, prototyped and implemented business specific data objects, production-facing tools, and services.
- · Structured and automated operational workflows.
- · Heavily expanded test-coverage and took responsibility for monitoring and resolving test related issues for the weekly releases.
- Built tool for maintenance, management and communication for Solactive's testsystems.
- Built an archiving solution for Solactive's FTP servers for daily processing of client files.

UWC Mahindra College Pune,India

SECRETARY OF THE COLLEGE ASSEMBLY

Mar. 2018 - Jan. 2019

- Facilitated, supported, and coordinated all activities of the student council.
- Developed, promoted, and conducted a variety of extra curricular programs for students.
- · Organized and coordinated various fundraising programs and funfair events to generate revenue.

Leave No Fingerprints Mumbai.India

HEAD OF MANAGEMENT AND ORGANISATION

Mar. 2017 - June. 2019

- · Organised multiple comedy events and concerts to raise money for purchasing equipment and dialysis machines for local hospitals.
- Developed and maintained the frontend functionality of websites.

Honors & Awards

Runner Up, T.C.S IT Wiz	Pune,India
Da Vinci Scholar, World Scholar's Cup	Delhi, India
1st Place, CISCE National Debate Final	Kolkata,India
Student of The Year, Anand Niketan School	Ahmedabad, India
	Da Vinci Scholar, World Scholar's Cup 1st Place, CISCE National Debate Final

Skills

Programming Experienced: Python, Java, Typescript Basic: C, C++, Haskell

Tools Experienced: Git, Grafana, Jenkins, ELK Basic: Docker, Kubernetes, RabbitMQ

Front-end Experienced: HTML5, CSS Basic: React, Vue Languages Native: English, Hindi Basic: German

Extracurricular Activity _____

Computers for All Pune, India

SERVICE PROGRAM CO-ORDINATOR Aug. 2017 - Jan. 2019

· Set up a functional computer lab and gave basic computer education to people of all age groups in the village of Asade.

PARTH SHUKLA · RÉSUMÉ MARCH 15, 2022